<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KonFuzed Banda</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KonFuzed Banda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 23:01:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring a Fresh Ubuntu Install for Coders</title>
      <link>/2017/11/configuring-a-fresh-ubuntu-install-for-coders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 23:01:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/configuring-a-fresh-ubuntu-install-for-coders/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Linux noob content below.
 How to create a sound coding environment after a fresh ubuntu install While I have been a coding enthusiast and Ubuntu has been my choice of OS as a hobbyist, I have always wanted to have a consistent coding environment across my installations without having to hunt for settings and configurations over the internet. Here I laid out a simple script with basic install procedures of various packages which has helped me and I would recommend for newbies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy DotNetCore SelfContained App Without Installing Runtime on Ubuntu Part2</title>
      <link>/2017/11/deploy-dotnetcore-selfcontained-app-without-installing-runtime-on-ubuntu-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:53:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/deploy-dotnetcore-selfcontained-app-without-installing-runtime-on-ubuntu-part2/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Linux noob content below.
 Part 2: Using Visual Studio 2017 with better tooling and bugfixes. How to publish dotnet core apps to ubuntu without installing dotnet runtime: self contained apps development
As a continuation of the previous post I tried to do the same with VS 2017 which supposedly has better tooling for Dot Net Core. I did also see the cspoj and xml structures were altered ( maybe for good - I am too noob to comment); but long story short, I had to dig around to get it working and compile the correct platform specific runtimes binaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy DotNetCore SelfContained App Without Installing Runtime on Ubuntu Part1</title>
      <link>/2017/11/deploy-dotnetcore-selfcontained-app-without-installing-runtime-on-ubuntu-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:13:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/deploy-dotnetcore-selfcontained-app-without-installing-runtime-on-ubuntu-part1/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Linux noob content below.
 Part 1: Using Visual Studio 2015 which has a different tooling than 2017 How to publish dotnet core apps to ubuntu without installing dotnet runtime: self contained apps development? I started exploring this option driven by a specific need. I have a bunch of applications and classes already available on different C# .NET projects scattered all over the place. Many of these libraries include complex neumerical functions, database transactions classes and image processing codes all written in C#.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install DotNetCore Ubuntu</title>
      <link>/2017/11/install-dotnetcore-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 23:47:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/install-dotnetcore-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Warning: Linux noob content below.
 Ubuntu 16.04 While most of the install instructions for .NET core works from the microsoft website it is vastly generic for all versions of Linux distros available. Here I tried to install on a Ubuntu 16.04 LTS and faced some issues. Of course .NET Core itself is pretty new and expecting standard versioning and dependency management across distros might be challenging even for Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>/page/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 21:05:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/hello/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Second Post</title>
      <link>/2017/11/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 21:01:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/11/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>